hiring teachers is not an easy job
anymore
HR faces the dilemma of resume overload
more than 40-thousand recruitment
websites and social media pages serve
job seekers a school receives between 85
to 140 resumes a day that equates to a
resume every three minutes based on an
eight-hour working day it is an
exhausting job to go through and select
a suitable candidates wouldn't it be
easier if you could only receive matched
resumes focus on the quality without
missing out on the suitable candidates
your answer is Prudential first match a
patent-pending filter and match
cloud-based technology we call this
tinder of recruitment although our
system is slightly more complicated than
swiping left and right on your phone but
you get the drift it is so simple that
anyone can start using it in minutes and
it saves time and resources only the
most suitable candidates for the job the
filter and match technology searches
through our existing candidate pool for
instant pick and the technology is
seamlessly embedded behind your website
to filter and match all future
applicants unsuitable applicants will be
stored in an account accessible at any
time in the future as hiring criteria
changes you can run the filter and match
again to see if any of those candidates
qualify effective and quick log on to
your account alter some questions to
activate the filter process and make a
few selections to match candidates it's
that simple the filter and match
technology goes through thousands of
candidates to bring you the right ones
instantaneously and activates filter and
match for all candidates applying until
you fill the position the Prudential
first match consolidates your hiring
process and widens your applicant pool
who will find the right candidate
applicants find their dream jobs our
candidate pool increases with each
school signup a win-win situation to
subscribe to Prudential first match
technology get in touch with our
friendly consultants today
start hiring the most suitable
candidates for your school